

francisco.dev

ABOUT ME

I'm Francisco Antu Almonacid Cammarata, a 24 years old developer who has the objective of developing, testing, and maintaining personal and enterprise applications.

Ultimately, it is my dream to be part of a team where I can actively contribute to building what matters while learning and honing my skills.

I always want to learn more and do more. I'm also a firm believer that we should never settle. I'm hard working, super curious, passionate, committed and a fast learner!

EDUCATION

Computer Engineering

Universidad Nacional de La Plata - Argentina 09/2022 - Current

Python

Coderhouse

03/2023 - 06/2023

English

Gateway School of English - La Valeta, Malta

Technical degree in agricultural production / High **School**

High School of Technical and Professional Education No. 733 "Benito Owen" - Gaiman, Argentina

SKILLS

Back-end: Skilled in Object-Oriented

Programming (OOP) in Python and

JavaScript, and specializing in the utilization

of frameworks such as Django and Flask.

Knowledgeable in working with databases,

including Postgresql and SQL.

Front-ent: Skilled at making websites look

both good and representative with

JavaScript, CSS, Bootstrap, and Tailwind CSS.

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

antudev.pythonanywhere.com/

- A sophisticated online platform designed as a virtual retail hub, allowing producer @antu.beats to display and showcase his extensive inventory of instrumentals.
- In the backend configuration, I addressed the management of authentication, registration, password change, and payments in Django, integrating MercadoPago API configuration for secure and efficient payment processing. I addressed model management to allow the publication of different products. Furthermore, I configured the cart for its proper functioning in the store.
- On the frontend I created an intuitive design, secure access, easy registration, interactive store with integrated payment experience using html5 and css3.

Web Developer

trenzaslaplata.onrei 10/2023 - Current

- Online catalog that allows the brand @trenzas.laplata to share the price list of its different services and share valuable information about their work
- In Flask I configured a postgresql database connection, defined braiding and price model, routes to display prices and braiding types, and a chatbot function to answer questions.
- The frontend uses HTML, CSS and JavaScript to create a responsive web page with a drop-down menu, informational sections and an integrated chatbot.

Web Developer

github.com/antu2809/ProyectoFinalAlmonacid

- The backend provides functions for adding customers, managing an online store, processing purchases, displaying images, and getting information from Instagram.
- The frontend features an elegant interface with personalized greetings, an art gallery, store and social links, and search functionalities.

Web Developer

franciscoantualmonacid.pythonanywhere.com/03/2024 - 04/2023

- I configured Flask routes for an online portfolio. It includes error handling, contact form validation, and email functionality. Backend logic retrieves project details and manages form submissions.
- HTML templates utilize Tailwind CSS classes for styling and layout. JavaScript is used for menu toggling, theme switching, and scroll animations using ScrollReveal.js. This combination enhances user experience and aesthetics in the Flask project's frontend.

SOCIALS

franciscoantualmonacid.pythonny where.com/

franciscoantualmonacid @gmail.com

github.com/antu2809

https://www.linkedin.com/in/fran cisco-almonacid-cammarata-543119267/